softworld.com 2016-01-26

# Softworld

At Softworld.com we are commited to respect and protect your online privacy. This includes your need and your right to know what we do with the personal information you share with us. It also guides our company’s policies regarding the management of this data, including how the information is collected, processed, and for what purposes. 

By accessing this website you are consenting to the way information is collected and used, as described within this Privacy Policy. 

Please note that some of the softwares listed on our website are downloaded directly from the developer website. Softworld.com cannot be held liable for issues that arise from the download or use of the software products. We encourage you to determine whether this software or your intended use is legal. Even if we try to check the program files for viruses, we cannot guarantee 100% that they are clean. For your own protection always check downloaded files for viruses, spyware and malware. 

Every time you log on to our website your IP (Internet Protocol) address registers on our servers. Your IP address reveals no information other than the number assigned to you. We do not use this technology to get any personal data against your knowledge or free will (i.e., automatically recording e-mail addresses of visitors). Nor do we use it for any purpose other than to help us monitor traffic on our website, or (in case of criminal activity or misuse of our information) to cooperate with law enforcement. 

Like many other Web sites, Softworld.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance. 

The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari etc.) 

Softworld.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**Google Analytics:**   
We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at <http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html>. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Softworld.com
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Softworld.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>
  
Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology for the advertisements and links that appear on Softworld.com to send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

Softworld.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. To opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. 

## Other Third Party Cookies

These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site that allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook and Google+. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website. You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.
